# **Upjeet Baswan**

#### Professional Summary

Hardworking and reliable general laborer with 3+ years of experience in warehouse, construction, and landscaping settings. Skilled in using hand and power tools, operating machinery, and performing manual labor tasks efficiently and safely. Strong ability to work in a team environment and follow instructions closely. Physically fit and able to lift heavy objects on a regular basis. Seeking a position where I can utilize my skills to contribute to a productive and successful team.



- upjeet1609@gmail.com
- 9 16 Chopin Crescent, Brampton, Canada
- github.com/UB-666

- . +1 2896230071
- upjeet.site
- instagram.com/0fficial\_ub

# **EDUCATION**

## **Computer Programing**

Pursuing an undergraduate degree in Computer Programming at Niagara College, Toronto.

01/2023 - Present

**High School Diploma in non-medical** DOABA ARYA SEN SEC SCHOOL NAWANSHAHR "Punjab"

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **WAREHOUSE ASSOCIATE**

Astron Onsite

01/2022 - 04/2022

1/2022 - 04/2022

Achievements/Tasks
Prepared orders for shipment by systematically picking, packing, and labeling merchandise.
Manually or mechanically loaded and unloaded materials from pallets, skids, platforms, cars, lifting devices, or other transport vehicles, Ms Office, Customer Service, Sales and Marketing,

Interpersonal, Excellent Communication, Team Building and Mentorship, Interpersonal skills, Packaging, Receiving

## **Restaurant Team Member**

Dixie Sweets & Restaurant

06/2022 - 11/2022

Brampton, ON

Brampton, ON

Achievements/Tasks

 Excellent communication skills Used cash registers and calculators to prepare bills, accept payments and make change.
Replenish condiments and other supplies at tables and serving areas - Clear and clean tables, trays and chairs - Balance cash and record sales - Assist customers with special needs - Customer service oriented
Helped large volume of customers every day with positive attitude and focus on customer satisfaction.
Described product highlights and benefits to help guide purchasing decisions.

## **Warehouse Worker**

F&P, Tottenham, ON

01/2023 - 03/2023

Tottenham, ON

#### Achievements/Tasks

 Loaded, unloaded and moved material to and from storage and production areas. • • Wrapped pallets in shrink wrap prior to loading.
Consistently lifted materials weighing as much as 40pounds. • Labeled and accurately moved customer orders to meet shipment timetables and minimize errors.

# SKILLS

Wrapping and Boxing

Machine Operations

Геатwork

Safety awareness

me management

Communication skills

Cash Counting

Attention to detail

Technical skills

## **AVAILABILITY**

Full-time and part time

## **SHIFTS**

Early Morning, Morning, Evening, Overnight.

#### **LANGUAGES**

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Punjabi and Hindi.

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

French

Elementary Proficiency